cinemark.com 2019-12-22

# Cinemark Privacy Policy

**_Cinemark Privacy Policy_**

Privacy Policy Effective August 26, 2019

Personal information provided to us at cinemark.com and Cinemark mobile app prior to the Effective Date is governed by our previous policy.

Privacy and Security

At cinemark.com and Cinemark mobile app, our policy is to protect the confidentiality of the individually identifiable information that you provide. The information we collect from you is used to process your orders and to provide you with a more personalized, quick, convenient shopping and rewards experience.

What kinds of information do we collect and how do we use it?

To process your ticket purchase and to notify you of your order status, we need to know your full name, e-mail address, credit card number and expiration date and, to the extent permitted by law, ZIP code. Your street address and telephone number may be required when necessary for shipping and delivery of your order of movie tickets, gift cards, Supersavers discounts, rewards, and/or merchandise.  In addition, if you choose to complete certain forms, provide us with optional information, or send us requests, you may be asked to provide the following information: street (mailing) address, city, state, ZIP, mobile phone number, and/or birthday (but not year). We use your orders to make your future shopping experience more convenient and to determine your preferences for purposes of making recommendations and to determine your rewards from third parties that might be of interest or of value to you. We may also collect information through cookies and automated computer information, as described below.

If you elect to register as a patron, we will require your name, e-mail address, street (mailing) address, city, state, ZIP, and mobile phone number.  As a registered patron, we will use this information for our general marketing purposes, but we will NOT call your mobile phone for marketing purposes.  As a registered patron, you will also receive our marketing materials via the street and/or e-mail addresses you provide, although you can unsubscribe (opt out) of those mailings at any time.  Please note that it may take up to ten (10) business days after we receive your opt-out for it to take effect.  If you opt-out of receiving emails about recommendations or other information we think may interest you, we may still send you e-mails about your account or any services you have requested or received from us.

If you agree to this Privacy Policy, we may use the personally identifiable information you disclose for Cinemark’s marketing purposes, including selling that information to third parties for their marketing purposes.  **_For Nevada residents_** , you may opt out at any time from the sale of your information to third parties by submitting a verified request to us at cinemark.com/my-personal-information directing us that we do not sell to third parties any of your information that we have collected or will collect about you.  The effect of your opt-out will be to prevent us from selling your information to third parties in exchange for financial consideration.  Your opt-out will NOT affect the information we collect about you or use for Cinemark’s own purposes.

You can review and change the individually identifiable personal information you provide to us at any time by clicking on My Profile. We are also constantly seeking to improve the layout and operation of cinemark.com based on the areas people visit, enjoy, and use most. We may occasionally wish to notify you about important changes to cinemark.com, new services, and special offers we think you might find valuable.

Information we collect also includes the IP address or other unique identifier (“Device Identifier”) for any computer, mobile phone, tablet or other device (any of which are referred to herein as a “Device”) used to access cinemark.com and use the Cinemark mobile app.  A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to your Device, and our servers identify your Device by its Device Identifier.  Some mobile service providers may also provide us or our third party service providers with information regarding the physical location of the Device used to access cinemark.com and use the Cinemark mobile app.  We may use Device Identifier information for a variety of purposes, including enhancing or otherwise improving cinemark.com and the Cinemark mobile app and our products and services. Device Identifier information is generally non-identifying, but if we associate it with you as a specific and identifiable person, we treat it as personal information. 

We may supplement the information we collect about you with outside records from third parties in order to provide you with information, services, or goods you have requested, to enhance our ability to serve you, and to tailor our content to you. We may combine the information we receive from those other sources with information we collect through cinemark.com and Cinemark mobile app. In those cases, we will apply this privacy policy to the combined information.

How does cinemark.com protect the information we collect?

When you place orders, the information is sent via an encrypted connection designed to protect the information you send to us so that it is scrambled as it travels over the Internet. Once your information arrives safely at cinemark.com and Cinemark mobile app, it is encrypted in storage. Our policy is to limit access to that information only to those with a need to know. However, keep in mind that there is no such thing as perfect security.

What about "cookies"?

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer. We added this optional feature to enable you to order more quickly. Cookies are not required in order for you to purchase tickets at cinemark.com or Cinemark mobile app, however they do enhance the user experience by storing your ZIP Code information to expedite the process of finding the movies you want to see in your area. In addition, most Web browsers can automatically store cookies on your computer, but you can usually change your browser to prevent it. Whatever you decide about cookies and/or the convenience features we offer, you will always be able to browse and order from cinemark.com and Cinemark mobile app. 

In addition to cookies, we also use at cinemark.com and Cinemark mobile app:

  * _Web Beacons_. These are small graphic images or other web programming code called web beacons (also known as “1x1 GIFs” or “clear GIFs”) that may be included in our web pages and e-mail messages. Web beacons may be invisible to you, but any electronic image or other web programming code inserted into a web page or e-mail can act as a web beacon. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to cinemark.com, to monitor how users navigate cinemark.com, as an identifier, to count how many e-mails that were sent were actually opened or to count how many particular articles or links were actually viewed.
  * _Embedded Scripts._ An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with cinemark.com and Cinemark mobile app, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your device from our web server or a third party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the cinemark.com and Cinemark mobile app, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.

Third parties may collect online information through pixel tags and cookies, which are used to create interest segments for marketing/advertising.    If you'd like to opt out of advertising cookies and trackers please click < <http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1>>.

Computer Information

We log your current Internet address (this is usually a temporary address assigned by your Internet service provider when you log in), the type of operating system, the type of browser software and the type of mobile device being used. In addition, we may keep track of which areas of cinemark.com or Cinemark mobile app you are visiting. We aggregate this information to help us improve or create a better experience for users of cinemark.com or Cinemark mobile app. For example: we may upgrade those parts of cinemark.com that are heavily visited. Our website and mobile app automatically records usage information that we analyze statistically to track operational problems, to prevent fraud and to improve the effectiveness, security and integrity of the website and mobile app. We will disclose this information to third parties only in aggregate form or as may be required by law. For each page that you visit, we collect and store the following technical information:

  * Date and time of access
  * URL address of the cinemark.com webpage visited
  * Internet domain and IP address from which cinemark.com was accessed
  * Type of browser and operating system used to access cinemark.com (if provided by the browser)
  * URL address of the referring page (if provided by the browser)
  * Completion or success status of the request for a web page or other on-line item
  * File size of the webpage visited

For the purpose of enabling better website design and a better user experience, we employ Google Analytics to track website traffic and provide aggregate reports of how the public interacts with our website. Session cookies are employed by Google Analytics in the form of client-side JavaScript code. In utilizing this analytics service, we maintain our existing standards in regards to the sharing and disclosure of information, security and privacy safeguards for the data, and the data retention policy, each described below. Google Analytics analyzes website usage information automatically upon visits to cinemark.com. Users who do not wish to have their visit information collected by Google Analytics may opt-out by downloading a browser extension or by disabling cookies in their browser settings. Opting-out of web measurements will still permit users to access cinemark.com, with all included information and functionality.

Tracking

As described in the “Computer Information” section above, we use Google Analytics. We may also permit Google Analytics to make use of a feature called User-ID. This functionality allows for more accurate analytics by using the same user identifier over various sessions and devices, including session unification of your interactions prior to logging in to the Site if you login during that same session. However, it is not intended to allow Google to personally identify an individual or permanently identify a particular device. No personal information is shared with Google.

We will not respond to Web browser "do not track" signals. If you would like additional information about online tracking and various opt-out mechanisms, please see donottrack.us. If you use the Chrome browser, you may opt out using the Chrome browser extension link <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>

Because we link to social media sites, and from time to time may include third-party advertisements, other parties may collect your personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different web sites when you visit cinemark.com.

If you want to opt out of the cookies placed by or on behalf of Cinemark (first party cookies) please click cinemark.com/clear-cookies.  Note that this link is only for cookies that are placed by or on behalf of Cinemark and does not clear third party cookies. 

If you would like additional information about online tracking and various opt-out mechanisms, please see <http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1>

Please note that not all tracking will stop even if you delete cookies.

Sharing Information with Third Parties

Does cinemark.com share the information it collects with others?

Unless you are a Nevada resident and you opt-out, we may sell your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes.

We may enter into joint marketing arrangements with third parties, such as movie studios.  If you consent to share your personally identifiable information, we will share your information with that joint marketer and the joint marketer may share your information with us.  There may be separate terms and conditions or a privacy policy for the joint marketing arrangement, which may be required if you wish to participate in the joint marketing arrangement (such as combining rewards programs). If you do not consent, we will not share your personally identifiable information with the joint marketer.

In addition, we may disclose personally identifiable information you provide to third parties if we are required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (a) complete a sales/reward transaction, such as providing your shipping information to our carrier; (b) enable third parties to assist us in operating, evaluating or improving cinemark.com and/or the Cinemark mobile app and/or our business; (c) comply with legal process; (d) enforce the Agreement; (e) respond to claims that any information you provide violates the rights of third parties; (f) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Cinemark, its users and/or the public; or (g) in relation to the sale, assignment, transfer or acquisition of all or substantially all of Cinemark's assets or shares by a third party.

Also, Cinemark.com and Cinemark mobile app may provide combined, general statistics about our customers, sales, usage patterns, and related information to reputable third parties, but these statistics will include no personal identifying information.

Consent & Changes to this Privacy Policy

By using cinemark.com and/or clicking "I agree," you consent to the collection and use of this information by cinemark.com and Cinemark mobile app. We reserve the right to change this privacy policy from time to time at our sole discretion and without sending notice to you, so you should review this privacy policy periodically. The effective date of this notice and any revised or changed notice may be found on this page, on the upper left hand corner of the notice. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it.  Any changes will be effective only after the effective date of the change, and will not affect any dispute arising prior to the effective date of the change.

Refund

Tickets that are purchased on Cinemark.com and the Cinemark mobile app with a registered account are able to be fully refunded on Cinemark.com up to two hours prior to the start of the showtime. At the theatre, a full refund can be given up to the start time of the showtime. In the rare situations when a show is cancelled, you will be entitled to a refund for the full purchase price of your tickets including any service charges. In these situations please notify our guest services department at Contact Us and include the theatre, movie, showtime, email address and your confirmation number.

Children and Minors

Cinemark makes no active effort to collect personal information from children under the age of 13 and does not wish to receive any such information.

Additional Rights:

Applicable laws may give you additional rights that are not described in this online privacy policy.

For further information on privacy matters contact our guest services department at Contact Us.

Contact Us: For further information, or inquiries about the Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy, please contact our guest services department at Contact Us.
